<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FitnessApp</string>
    <string name="fitness_buddy"><b>Fitness Buddy</b></string>
    <string name="username"><b>Username</b></string>
    <string name="password"><b>Password</b></string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="achtergrond">Achtergrond</string>
    <string name="choose">Choose</string>
    <string name="cardio">Cardio</string>
    <string name="heavy_lifting">Heavy Lifting</string>
    <string name="calisthetics">Calisthetics</string>
    <string name="endurance">Endurance</string>
    <string name="streches">Stretches</string>
    <string name="debug">debug</string>
    <string name="niks">niks</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="popupText">Username invalid or not available \n\nClick anywhere to continue</string>
    <string name="popupTextFail"> Account has been created! \n\nClick anywhere to continue</string>
    <string name="please_only_use_letters_and_numbers_for_username"><b>Please only use letters and numbers for username</b></string>
    <string name="nog_geen">nog geen</string>
    <string name="title">title</string>
    <string name="cardio2"><b>Cardio</b></string>
    <string name="lifting2"><b>Heavy Lifting</b></string>
    <string name="Calisthenics2"><b>Calisthenics</b></string>
    <string name="Streches2"><b>Streches</b></string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="Strech1">Stand tall with your feet hip-width apart, knees slightly bent, arms by your sides.\n\nExhale as you bend forward at the hips, lowering your head toward floor, while keeping your head, neck and shoulders relaxed.\n\nWrap your arms around backs of your legs and hold anywhere from 45 seconds to two minutes.\n\nBend your knees and roll up when you\'re done.</string>
    <string name="Strech2">Sit on the floor with both legs extended in front of you.\n\nCross your right leg over your left, and place your right foot flat on the floor.\n\nPlace your right hand on the floor behind your body.\n\nPlace your left hand on your right quad or your left elbow on your right knee (as shown) and press your right leg to the left as you twist your torso to the right.\n\nIf the spinal rotation bothers your back, take it out and simply use your left hand to pull your right quad in and to the left.</string>
    <string name="Strech3">Stretching keeps the muscles flexible, strong, and healthy, and we need that flexibility to maintain a range of motion in the joints. \nWithout it, the muscles shorten and become tight. Then, when you call on the muscles for activity, they are weak and unable to extend all the way.\nThat puts you at risk for joint pain, strains, and muscle damage.</string>
    <string name="Strech4">Kneel, sit, or stand tall with feet hip-width apart, arms extended overhead.\n\nBend your right elbow and reach your right hand to touch the top middle of your back.\n\nReach your left hand overhead and grasp just below your right elbow.\n\nGently pull your right elbow down and toward your head.\n\nSwitch arms and repeat.</string>
    <string name="Strech5">Sit on the floor with your knees bent and feet flat on the floor.\n\nClasp your hands behind your lower back.\n\nStraighten and extend your arms and squeeze your shoulder blades together.\n\nDo this for 3 seconds, and then release. Repeat 5 to 10 times.\n\n Note: The Triceps stretch could also be used to stretch your Shoulders</string>
    <string name="Strech6">Sit with bent knees and your feet flat on the floor in front of your hips.\n\nPlace your hands on the floor behind you with your fingers facing away from your body.\n\nEvenly distribute your weight between your feet, buttocks, and arms.\n\nSlowly scoot your buttocks forward, toward your feet, without moving your hands.\n\nHold this position for up to 30 seconds.\n\nReturn to the starting position and relax for a few moments.</string>
    <string name="Strech7">Kneel on your left knee. Place your right foot flat on the floor in front of you, knee bent.\n\nLean forward, stretching your left hip toward the floor.\n\nSqueeze your butt; this will allow you to stretch your hip flexor even more.\n\nHold for 30 seconds to 2 minutes.\n\nSwitch sides and repeat.</string>
    <string name="insert_playlist_link_and_update">Insert playlist link and Update!</string>
    <string name="click_one_of_the_catagories_to_update_your_data">Click one of the catagories to update your data!</string>
    <string name="invalid_username_or_password"><b>Invalid username or password</b></string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="current_selection">Current selection:</string>
</resources>